Guide to the Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions Records, Addendum
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Publications and Literature Distribution Addendum, Series VII
  - Committee Records
    - Manuscript of For This Hour by E.H. Johnson, March 26, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 448)
    - Order Blanks for Published Works, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 449)
    - Papers rejected by Motive including Early Protestant Views of Hinduism 1600-1825 by Norvin Hein (Box 44, Folder 450)
    - Publications and Outlines from Other Organizations, 1949-1959 (Box 44, Folder 451)
    - Publications from other Student Christian Movements, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 452)
    - Purchase Orders and Invoices, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 453)
    - Quotations for Multi-Lithed Cooley Manuscript, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 454)
    - Remittance Sheets, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 455)
    - Remittance Sheets, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 456)
    - Report of Commission VII -- The Christian Community Through a World Wide Program and Miscellaneous Essays (Box 44, Folder 457)
    - Requests for Materials, 1946 (Box 44, Folder 458)
    - Shaull Manuscript with Comments, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 459)
    - Stock Inventory, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 460)
    - With Schweitzer in Africa, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 461)
  - Publications
    - The Achievements of the Student Volunteer Movement During the First Generation of its History 1886-1919; The First Two Decades of the Student Volunteer Movement, 1906, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 462)
    - Brochures, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 463)
    - Christian Horizons (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - History of the Student Volunteer Movement by John Mott; The Student Volunteer Movement: Its History, Genius, and Present Organization by Gordon Poteat; The Student Volunteer Movement: Its Origin and Early History by Robert P. Wilder, 1892, 1928, 1935 (Box 45, Folder 464)
    - Plays: Ba Thane: a One Act Play of Burma; Where Hope is Born: a Play for Student Relief, 1940, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 465)
    - Report of the First International Convention of the Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions Held at Cleveland, Ohio; Report of the Executive Committee of the Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions Presented at the Third International Convention Held at Cleveland, Ohio, 1891, 1898 (Box 45, Folder 466)
    - The...Student Volunteer: Official Organ of the Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Movement Vol. 1 No. 1- Vol. 3 No. 8 (missing Vol. 1 No. 2), 1893-1895 (Box 45, Folder 467)
    - The...Student Volunteer: Official Organ of the Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions Vol. 3 No. 9-Vol. 5 No. 9, 1895-1897 (Box 45, Folder 468)
    - The...Student Volunteer: Official Organ of hte Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions Vol. 6 No. 1-Vol. 6 No. 5, 1897-1898 (Box 45, Folder 469)
    - Student Volunteer Series Pamphlets, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 470)
    - Volunteer (Box 11, Folder 94)
- Conventions Addendum, Series VIII
  - Wooster, Ohio (1943-1944)
    - Continental Student Conference on World Mission of the Church (proposed) and Tentative Budget, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 472)
    - Planning Minutes, 1942-1943 (Box 46, Folder 471)
  - Lawrence, Kansas (1947-1948)
    - Accounts and Purchase Requests (Box 46, Folder 473)
    - Handbook for Leaders of Froncon in Miniature (Box 46, Folder 474)
    - Prepratory Materials and Memos (Box 46, Folder 475)
    - Records (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 46, Folder 476)
    - Report of Froncon Evaluation Meeting, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 477)
  - Lawrence, Kansas (1951-1952)
    - Administrative and Budget Documents (Box 11, Folder 95-97)
    - Administrative Committee (Box 46, Folder 478)
    - Budget (Box 46, Folder 479)
    - Budget Planning (Box 46, Folder 480)
    - Conference Planning (Box 46, Folder 481)
    - Evaluations (Box 46, Folder 482)
    - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 46, Folder 483)
    - Memos, E.H. Johnson's Statement, Miscellaneous Minutes, and Follow Up Mateterials (Box 46, Folder 484)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - Play: In His Hands by Archie Crouch (Box 47, Folder 485)
    - Post Conference Plans (Box 47, Folder 486)
    - Press Materials for Scrapbook (Box 47, Folder 487)
    - Press Releases (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - Publication Committee Minutes (Box 47, Folder 488)
    - Publications Promoting Quadrennial Conference (Box 47, Folder 489)
    - Race Discrimination and World Mission of the Church Study Paper (Box 47, Folder 490)
    - Registration Procedures (Box 47, Folder 491)
    - Roster of Delegates (Box 47, Folder 492)
    - Statistical Report (Box 47, Folder 493)
    - Strategy Committee (Box 47, Folder 494)
    - Study Program Committee Minutes (Box 47, Folder 495)
  - Athens, Ohio (1955-1956)
    - Administrative and Budget Documents (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - Area Forums, Seminars, and Evaluations (Box 47, Folder 496)
    - Art Work (Box 47, Folder 497)
    - Articles Pre and Post Conference (Box 47, Folder 498)
    - Bible Discussion Groups -- Correspondence and Evaluations (Box 47, Folder 499)
    - Bible Study Preparations (Box 48, Folder 500)
    - Budget (Box 48, Folder 501)
    - Budget (Complete) (Box 48, Folder 502)
    - Budget Expenses (Box 48, Folder 503)
    - Budget (Tentative) (Box 48, Folder 504)
    - Campus Delegation Meetings -- Notes and Thoughts (Box 48, Folder 505)
    - Conference Bulletins (Box 48, Folder 506)
    - Conference Materials for Participants (Box 48, Folder 507)
    - Contributions to Quadrennial Budget (Box 48, Folder 508)
    - Correspondence re. Conference Bookstore (Box 48, Folder 509)
    - Correspondence re. Communion Service (Box 48, Folder 510)
    - Correspondence re. Publications for Conference (Box 48, Folder 511)
    - Correspondence re. Publicity Plans and Announcements (Box 48, Folder 512)
    - Correspondence re. Telephone and Telegraph Communications (Box 48, Folder 513)
    - Correspondence re. USCC/WSCF Member Movement Meetings (Box 48, Folder 514)
    - Daily Program Emphasis (Box 48, Folder 515)
    - Directory (Box 48, Folder 516)
    - Drama Committee (Box 48, Folder 517)
    - Ecumenical Student Conference Account at Bank of Athens (Ohio) (Box 49, Folder 518)
    - Evaluations (Box 49, Folder 519)
    - Exhibits and Bookstore (Box 49, Folder 520)
    - Film and Performances (Box 49, Folder 521)
    - Financial Adjustments (Refunds) (Box 49, Folder 522)
    - Firesides Committee (Box 49, Folder 523)
    - Forms (Box 49, Folder 524)
    - General Follow Up (Box 49, Folder 525)
    - Hospitality (Box 49, Folder 526)
    - Insurance Information (Box 49, Folder 527)
    - List of Receipts Indicating Financial Responsiblity (Box 49, Folder 528)
    - Literature and Study Committee (Box 49, Folder 529)
    - Local Arrangements (Box 49, Folder 530)
    - Master List of Conference Leaders (Box 49, Folder 531)
    - Memos re. Platform Leadership (Box 49, Folder 532)
    - Minutes of the Area Forum Sub-Committee, Exhibits, Mincon, and Officer and Staff Planning Group (Box 49, Folder 533)
    - Minutes of the Consultation on Worship (Box 49, Folder 534)
    - Miscellaneous Post Conference Comments and Activities (Box 49, Folder 535)
    - Miscellaneous Documents re. Conference Leaders, Publicity, etc (Box 49, Folder 536)
    - Miscellaneous Letters, Memos, and Telegrams (Box 49, Folder 537)
    - Miscellaneous Reports (Box 49, Folder 538)
    - Music at the Conference (Box 49, Folder 539)
    - NCCCUSA Vouchers, Memos (Box 49, Folder 540)
    - Paid Bills of Local Conference Expenses (Box 49, Folder 541)
    - Paper Speakers (Mostly on Revolution) (Box 49, Folder 542)
    - Planning Committee (Box 50, Folder 543)
    - Planning Committee Minutes (Box 50, Folder 544)
    - Post Conference Program Development Committee (Box 50, Folder 545)
    - Promotion/Publicity (Box 50, Folder 546)
    - Promotion/Publicity (Box 50, Folder 547)
    - Proposed Daily Program Emphasis (Box 50, Folder 548)
    - Proposed Leadership, Schedules, Speakers, and Themes (Box 50, Folder 549)
    - Recruitment (Box 50, Folder 550)
    - Retreat Group Meeting with M.A. Thomas (Box 50, Folder 551)
    - Seventeenth SVM Quadrennial Initial Consultation (Box 50, Folder 552)
    - Scholarships for Overseas Students (Box 50, Folder 553)
    - Scripts for Slide Sets (Box 51, Folder 554)
    - Statistics of Member Delegations (Box 51, Folder 554)
    - Study Book (Box 51, Folder 555)
    - Talent Performance (Box 51, Folder 556)
    - Travel Fund (Box 51, Folder 557)
    - Vocational Interviews (Box 51, Folder 558)
    - Vocational Seminar Evaluations and Analysis Reports (Box 51, Folder 559)
    - Vocational Seminars Statistics (Box 51, Folder 560)
    - Working Committee (Box 51, Folder 561)
    - Working Committee (Box 51, Folder 562)
    - Worship Committee (Box 51, Folder 563)
    - World Student Christian Federation Sponsorship (Box 51, Folder 564)
  - Athens, Ohio (1959-1960)
    - Account Book (Box 51, Folder 565)
    - Administration (Box 63, Folder 688)
    - Audio Visual Materials (Box 63, Folder 689)
    - Auditorium (Box 63, Folder 690)
    - Bible Study (Box 51, Folder 566)
    - Bible Study, Hymn Book, and Program of Conference (Box 51, Folder 567)
    - Biographical Sketches (Box 63, Folder 691)
    - Board Sponsored Personnel and Students (Box 63, Folder 692)
    - Book Store and Exhibits (Box 51, Folder 568)
    - Budget (Box 51, Folder 569)
    - Budget -- Receipts and Vouchers (Box 52, Folder 570)
    - Budget -- Record of Income and Expenditure Taken from NCCCUSA's Detailed Ledger (Box 52, Folder 571)
    - Budget -- Requests for Funding, Vouchers, and Account Sheets (Box 52, Folder 572)
    - Call for Participants for Festival of Nations (Box 63, Folder 693)
    - Campus Coordinators (Box 52, Folder 573)
    - Committee Memberships (Box 63, Folder 694)
    - Coordinators (Box 63, Folder 695)
    - Correspondence re. Bank Account (Box 52, Folder 574)
    - Correspondence re. Lost and Found (Box 52, Folder 575)
    - Directory (Box 52, Folder 576)
    - Dorm Business (Box 52, Folder 577)
    - Drama Committee (Box 63, Folder 696)
    - Evaluations (Box 52, Folder 578)
    - Excerpts from Speeches and Reports from Conference (Box 52, Folder 579)
    - Financial Contributions (Box 52, Folder 580)
    - Firesides (Box 63, Folder 697)
    - Frontiers (Box 53, Folder 581)
    - Interviewers (Box 53, Folder 582)
    - Leadership (Box 53, Folder 583)
    - Leadership (Box 63, Folder 698)
    - Letters and Telegrams Wishing for a Successful Conference (Box 53, Folder 584)
    - Local Arrangements (Box 53, Folder 585)
    - Local Arrangements (Box 63, Folder 699)
    - Medical (Box 63, Folder 700)
    - Music (Box 53, Folder 586)
    - News Releases (Box 53, Folder 587)
    - Ohio University Library Layout (Box 53, Folder 588)
    - Outlines for Conference Newspaper (Box 53, Folder 589)
    - Planning Committee (Box 53, Folder 590)
    - Planning Committee (Box 53, Folder 591)
    - Planning Committee (Box 53, Folder 592)
    - Possible Locations for Conference (Box 63, Folder 701)
    - Possible Speakers for Conference (Box 63, Folder 702)
    - Post Conference Publicity (Box 53, Folder 593)
    - Pre-Conference Publicity (Box 63, Folder 703)
    - Program (Box 53, Folder 594)
    - Program Materials (Box 53, Folder 595)
    - Promotion and Interpretation (Box 53, Folder 596)
    - Prospective Conference Papers (Box 53, Folder 597)
    - Record of Tapes Recorded and Films Used (Box 53, Folder 598)
    - Recruitment Committee (Box 63, Folder 704)
    - Registration (Box 54, Folder 598a)
    - Resource Material (Box 63, Folder 705)
    - Roster (Box 63, Folder 706)
    - Schedule (Box 63, Folder 707)
    - Scholarship (Box 54, Folder 599)
    - Scholarships Awarded (Box 63, Folder 708)
    - Sobell Case (Box 63, Folder 709)
    - Stewards (Box 54, Folder 600)
    - Study Materials (Box 63, Folder 710)
    - Summaries of Other Conferences (Box 54, Folder 601)
    - Thank yous (Box 54, Folder 602)
    - Theme and Content (Box 54, Folder 603)
    - Transportation (Box 63, Folder 711)
    - Travel Equalization (Box 63, Folder 712)
    - Travel Staff (Box 63, Folder 713)
    - Working Committee (Box 54, Folder 604)
    - Working Committee (Box 54, Folder 605)
    - Worship Committee (Box 54, Folder 606)
    - Working Staff (Box 63, Folder 714)
    - World Student Christian Federation (Box 54, Folder 607)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Clergy Applications (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - Staff Conferences (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - Summer Conferences (Box 12, Folder 103)
- Relationships with Other Organizations Addendum, Series IX
  - Agricultural Missions, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - American Baptist Convention -- Minister and Missionaries Benefit Board, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 608)
  - American Committee (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Baptist Student Movement (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Canadian Council of Churches: Commission on the Church and University (Box 54, Folder 609)
  - Chinese Students' Christian Association In North America (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Chinese Students' Chrisitan Association, September 11-14, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 610)
  - Christ for the World, 1948-1951 (Box 54, Folder 611)
  - Christian Medical Council for Overseas Work, 1946 (Box 54, Folder 612)
  - Church World Service, 1947 (Box 54, Folder 613)
  - Civilian Public Service Camps, 1942-1944 (Box 54, Folder 614)
  - Committee on Friedly Relations Among Foreign Students (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Committee on Friendly Relations Among Foreign Students, 1945-1952 (Box 54, Folder 615)
  - Council for Religion in Independent Schools (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Evangelical and Reformed Church Student Movement (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Federal Council of Churches, 1939-1950 (Box 55, Folder 615)
  - Federal Council of Churches, 1949-1950 (Box 55, Folder 616)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 1944-1948 (Box 55, Folder 617)
  - Foreign Missionary Work, 1928-1943 (Box 55, Folder 618)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America -- Committee on Missionary Personnel, 1946-1948 (Box 55, Folder 619)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North American -- Committee on Missionary Personnel, 1949-1950 (Box 55, Folder 620)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America -- Correspondence, 1940-1952 (Box 56, Folder 621)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America -- Missionary Personnel Needs, 1945 (Box 56, Folder 622)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America -- Missionary Personnel Needs, 1946 (Box 56, Folder 623)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America -- Proposals and Memos, 1948-1949 (Box 56, Folder 624)
  - Greater New York Council for Foreign Students (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Home Missions Council (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Home Missions Council -- Christian Approach to Jewish People, 1947-1948 (Box 56, Folder 625)
  - Home Missions Council -- Reports and Memos, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 626)
  - Home Missions Council -- Correspondence, 1945-1951 (Box 56, Folder 627)
  - Home Missions Council, 1945 (Box 56, Folder 628)
  - Intercollegian, 1944 (Box 56, Folder 629)
  - Intercollegian, 1945 (Box 56, Folder 630)
  - International Council of Religious Education (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - International Committee of the YMCA, 1948 (Box 57, Folder 633)
  - International Council of the Religious Education -- Committee on Youth and Student Work, 1943-1948 (Box 57, Folder 634)
  - International Missionary Council (Box 13, Folder 114-115)
  - International Missionary Council -- Correspondence, Quarterly Notes, 1946-1949 (Box 57, Folder 635)
  - International Missionary Council -- Correspondence, 1948-1951 (Box 57, Folder 636)
  - International Student Relief (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - Interseminary Movement -- Correspondence, Minutes, and Reports, 1943-1948 (Box 57, Folder 637)
  - Interseminary Movement -- Minutes and Report on ISM, 1947 (Box 57, Folder 638)
  - Invest Your Summer (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - IRM -- Bibliography, 1948 (Box 57, Folder 639)
  - Japan International Christian University (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Koinonia Foundation (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - Laymen's Missionary Movement, 1945-1951 (Box 57, Folder 640)
  - Lisle Fellowship, 1945 (Box 57, Folder 641)
  - Methodist Church, 1955-1959 (Box 57, Folder 642)
  - Methodist Student Movement (Box 14, Folder 120-121)
  - Methodist Student Movement, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 643)
  - Mission Medical Service (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - Missionary Education Movement (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Missionary Education Movement, 1941-1950 (Box 58, Folder 644)
  - Missionary Education Movement -- Board of Managers, 1947-1950 (Box 58, Folder 645)
  - Missionary Education Movement, 1949-1950 (Box 58, Folder 646)
  - Missionary Education Movement, 1948-1951 (Box 58, Folder 647)
  - Missionary Research Library (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - Movements on Mission (Box 15, Folder 125)
  - National Arts Club (Box 15, Folder 126)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ (Box 15, Folder 127-128)
  - NCCC -- By Laws, 1950 (Box 58, Folder 648)
  - NCCC: Christian Medical Council for Overseas Work (Box 15, Folder 129)
  - NCCC: Committee on World Literacy (Box 16, Folder 130)
  - NCCC: Committee on Research in Foreign Missions (Box 16, Folder 131)
  - NCCC -- Constitutions, General Assembly Workbook, Materials re. CCHE Restructuring, 195? (Box 59, Folder 649)
  - NCCC -- Organizing Committee Publications, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 650)
  - NCCC-SVM Relationship Documents (Box 18, Folder 152)
  - NCCC-SVM Merger, 1951-1952 (Box 59, Folder 651)
  - NCCC-SVM Merger, Memos, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 652)
  - NCCC-SVM Merger, 1950 (Box 59, Folder 653)
  - NCCC-SVM Merger, 1951 (Box 59, Folder 654)
  - NCCC-SVM Merger, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 655)
  - NCCC-SVM Relationship, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 656)
  - National Council Speakers Bureau, 1944 (Box 59, Folder 657)
  - National Intercollegiate Christian Council (Box 16, Folder 132)
  - National Lutheran Council (Box 16, Folder 133)
  - National Religious Publicity Council (Box 16, Folder 134)
  - National Stewardship Institute of the Golden Rule Foundation, 1947-1950 (Box 59, Folder 658)
  - National Student Christian Federation, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 659)
  - North American Administration Committee (Box 16, Folder 135)
  - Presbyterian Church/Westminster Foundation (Box 16, Folder 136-137)
  - Presbyterian Church in the USA -- Board of Forein Missions, 1941-1944 (Box 60, Folder 660)
  - Presbyterian Church in the USA -- Board of Foreign Missions, 1941-1945 (Box 60, Folder 661)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church (Box 17, Folder 138)
  - Southern Baptist Student Movement (Box 17, Folder 139)
  - Student Christian Movement in Canada (Box 17, Folder 140)
  - Student Christian Movement in Central Region (Lake Geneva, WI) (Box 17, Folder 141)
  - Student Christian Movement in Great Britain and Ireland (Box 17, Folder 142)
  - Student Christian Movement in India (Box 17, Folder 143)
  - Student Christian Movement in Mid-Atlantic Region (Box 17, Folder 144)
  - Student Christian Movement in New England Region (Box 17, Folder 145)
  - Student Christian Movement in New York Region (Box 18, Folder 146)
  - Student Christian Movement in Northwest Region (Box 18, Folder 147)
  - Student Christian Movement in Rocky Mtn Region (Box 18, Folder 148)
  - Student Christian Movement in Siam (Thailand) (Box 18, Folder 149)
  - Student Christian Movement in Southeast Region (Box 18, Folder 150)
  - Student Christian Movement in Southwest Region (Box 18, Folder 151)
  - United Christian Youth Movement, 1943-1944 (Box 60, Folder 662)
  - United Christian Youth Movement, 1951 (Box 60, Folder 663)
  - United Student Christian Council Campus Strategy Committee (Box 19, Folder 153-154)
  - USCC Committee on Religion in Higher Education (Box 19, Folder 155)
  - USCC Communique (Box 19, Folder 156)
  - USCC Conference Report Committee (Box 19, Folder 157)
  - USCC General Assembly (Box 19, Folder 158)
  - USCC Memos, Meetings, Reports, 1947-1955 (Box 60, Folder 664)
  - USCC Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 159)
  - USCC Quadrennial Program Committee Minutes, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 665)
  - USCC Program Reports (Box 20, Folder 160)
  - USCC Publications Committee (Box 20, Folder 161)
  - USCC Quadrennial Study Conferences (Box 20, Folder 162)
  - USCC Statement of Purpose and Relationship with SVM (Box 20, Folder 163)
  - USCC-SVM Consultation concerning X General Assembly 1953 (Box 20, Folder 164)
  - USCC-SVM Agreements re. Rent, Shared Equipment, and Services, 1947-1953 (Box 60, Folder 666)
  - USCC-SVM Relationship, 1953 (Box 60, Folder 667)
  - University Christian Commission, 1946-1947 (Box 61, Folder 668)
  - Westminster Fellowship, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 669)
  - World Alliance of YMCA -- World Youth Newsletter, 1941-1942 (Box 61, Folder 670)
  - World Council of Christian Education (Box 21, Folder 167)
  - World Council of Christian Education (Box 61, Folder 671)
  - World Council of Churches (Box 20, Folder 165)
  - World Council of Churches -- Youth Department (Box 61, Folder 672)
  - WCC: Ecumenical Work Camps (Box 20, Folder 166)
  - World Student Christian Federation (Box 21, Folder 168-169)
  - World Student Christian Federation Consultation, 1945 (Box 61, Folder 673)
  - WSCF General Committee Minutes, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 674)
  - World Student Service Fund (Box 21, Folder 170-171)
  - World Student Service Fund (folder 3) (Box 22, Folder 172)
  - World Student Service Fund, 1941-1942 (Box 61, Folder 675)
  - World Student Service Fund, 1942-1947 (Box 61, Folder 676)
  - World University Service (Box 22, Folder 173)
  - YMCA -- Correspondence, 1948 (Box 61, Folder 677)
  - YMCA National Student Office, 1942-1947 (Box 61, Folder 678)
  - YMCA/YWCA (Box 22, Folder 174-176)
  - YMCA/YWCA: Commission on World Relatedness (Box 23, Folder 177)
  - YMCA/YWCA: The President's School (Box 23, Folder 178)
  - Youth Work / Youth Department (Box 23, Folder 179-180)
  - Youth Service Projects (Box 23, Folder 181)
- Photographs, Series X
  - Slides and negatives of 16th Quadrennial (Box 24, Folder 184)
  - Photographs (Box 25, Folder 185-186)
  - 17th Quadrennial Conference Proofs, 1955-1956 (Box 61, Folder 679)
  - 18th Quadrennial Conference Miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (Box 61, Folder 680)
  - 18th Quadrennial Conference Miscellaneous including photographs of Bishop Lesslie Newbigin, Bola Ige, Martin Luther King, Jr, and Winburn Thomas, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 681)
  - 18th Quadrennial Conference Negatives, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 683)
  - 18th Quadrennial Conference Performances, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 684)
  - 18th Quadrennial Conference Performance and Worship Services, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 685)
  - 18th Quadrennial Press Photographs and Negatives of Bishop Lesslie Newbigin and Martin Luther King, Jr, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 686)
  - 18th Quadrennial Conference Proofs, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 687)
- Oversize Materials
  - 17th & 18th Quadrennial Conference Newspapers: The Ohio University Post, Conference Currents, and Frontier Post, 1955-1956, 1959-1960
  - Ledger Sheets, 1952-1953